Inan Bostanci's Resume"

Inan Bostanci

2022-04-10

Aside



Download a PDF of this CV

Contact

- $\bullet \quad i.e.bostanci@uu.nl \\$
- github.com/inanimate36inan-bostanci.netlify.app

Software Skills

R

Python

SPSS

Stata

MS Office

Language Skills

English

German

Turkish

French

Disclaimer

Made w/ pagedown.

Source code: github.com/nstrayer/cv.

Last updated on 2022-04-10.

Main

Inan Bostanci

Currently, I am interning and writing my thesis at Statistics Netherlands (CBS). In this research project, traffic loop sensor data and administrative data are utilised to improve models that estimate travel behavior and predict traffic on a nationwide level. The thesis is supervised by Dr. Peter Lugtig and Yvonne Gootzen.

Education

MSc Methodology and Statistics in the Behavioral, Biomedical and Social Sciences (in progress)

Utrecht University

Netherlands

2022 - 2020

• Thesis: Linking traffic loop sensors and administrative data to predict nationwide traffic

BA Sociology

Leipzig University

Germany

2020 - 2015

• Thesis: Using survey data and regional data to test for an effect of social networks on labour market outcomes

Employment History

Intern Data Science/Methodology in Mobility Research

DaCiMob

Statistics Netherlands (CBS)

2022 - 2021

- Working with big data for mobility research as part of my thesis
- Linking traffic loop sensor data, administrative data and infrastructure data to predict nationwide traffic for official statistics
- Writing scripts for data management and analysis of traffic loop sensor data

Research Assistant/Intern in T-NAMSE project

Institute for Public Health

Charité - Berlin University of Medicine

2020 - 2019

- Health service research project involving multiple research teams across Germany.
- Management, cost-analysis, plausibility checks, cleaning, statistical analysis and visualization of data
- Translating and communicating code from different software

Student Assistant

School of Media, Communication and Sociology

University of Leicester

2020 - 2017

- Research project Far-Right Environmental Risk Communication in the European Parliament
- Collecting, monitoring and coding data and parliamentary speeches of the EU parliament and of newspaper articles

Intern Behavioural Policy and Disruptive Technology

Ministry of Trade Ankara, Republic of Turkey 2019

- Assistance in Turkeys first Nudge Unit (applying behavioural science in public policy)
- Attendance in international meetings to implement blockchain technology in international trade
- Literature reviews

Student Assistant Chair of Institutions and Social Change

Institute for Sociology Leipzig University 2019 - 2018

- Data analysis and visualisation, data research, literature research
- Managing the learning management system
- Proof-reading and revising in English and German

Student Assistant in EU-funded SOLIDUS (Horizon 2020, grant agreement #649489)

Institute for Sociology Leipzig University

2018 - 2017

- Assisted in authoring of the "European Solidarity in Times of Crisis"-monograph
- Preparing and analysing reports
- Conducting and evaluating focus group meetings, interviews and national seminars

Teaching Assistant Methods and Statistics

Institute for Sociology Leipzig University 2017 - 2016

• Marking students homework in statistics and assisting in lectures